我们所有人之中  下一个结婚的会是谁
Out of all of us, who do you think will get married next?
大概是莫妮卡和钱德勒
Probably Monica and Chandler.
给我一包新港淡烟
Could I have a pack of Newport Lights, please?
我们不卖烟
We don't sell cigarettes,
对街开了个新报摊有卖
but they have them at the newsstand across the street.
太好了  谢谢
That'd be great. Thanks.
天啊
Oh, my god.
梅莉莎·伍伯  我没有力气应付她
Melissa Worbert. I don't think I have the energy for this.
天啊  瑞瑞·格林
Oh, my God! Ray-Ray Greene?
最近怎么样
What's up?!
你是我们姐妹会周报连续七期的焦点人物
You've been MIA for the past seven sorority newsletters.
你怎么样
What's up with you?
我们到那边去再说
Why don't I tell you over here?
上次我听说你要结婚了
So last I heard you were gonna get married.
可怜的瑞瑞
Poor Ray-Ray.
不  这其实很好
Oh, no. It's all good.
-我现在在拉夫罗兰工作  -闭嘴
- I actually work at Ralph Lauren. - Shut up!
我就不  我是男装运动服饰的分区主管
I will not. I'm the divisional head of men's sportswear.
再闭嘴  你和拉夫是朋友吗
Shut up more! Are you friends with Ralph?
-拜托  -你是吗
- Oh, please. - Are you?
不是
No.
我们一定要一起吃饭  你明天有什么安排
We have to have dinner. What are you doing tomorrow night?
明天  我不知道
Tomorrow. I don't know.
那就和我一起吃晚饭吧
You do now. You're having dinner with me.
闭嘴
Shut up.
我要走了  看到你真好  瑞瑞
I've gotta go. This has been so great, Ray-Ray.
你回来了
Oh, there you are.
-打电话给我  这是我的名片  -谢谢
- So listen, just call me. Here's my card. - Oh, wow, thanks.
-你在做房地产  -不  那是旧名片
- You're in real estate? - No, that's an old card.
我必须辞去那份工作  做些...
I want to get out of that to do something...
可以帮助别人  改变世界的工作
...where I could help people and make a difference.
现在你做什么
What do you do now?
宴会策划
I'm a party planner.
-明天见  -好
- I'll see you tomorrow. - Okay.
看谁回来了  是瑞瑞
Hey, guys. Look who's back. It's Ray-Ray.
那是我大学的朋友梅莉莎
That was my friend, Melissa, from college.
她看起来很有意思
She seems really, really fun!
她真的很可爱  我们曾经很亲近
She's actually very sweet, and we used to be very close.
等一下  她不会就是那个你...
Wait a minute. She's not the one who you...?
你怎么了  你怎么了
Who you what? Who you what?
-就是她  -哇
- Yes. - Wow!
哇什么  哇什么  你怎么她了
Wow, what? Wow, what? Who you what?
没什么大不了
Oh, it's not a big deal.
她们是情人
They were lovers.
-什么  -什么
- What? - What?
不  我们不是情人  根本没什么
No, we weren't. It was nothing.
大四的一天晚上  我们去参加舞会...
It was one night, senior year, and we went to a party...
喝了不少桑格利塔酒  结果...
...had a lot of sangria, and you know, ended up...
我们接吻了
...kissing for a bit.
我的两个老婆都是同性恋
So that's two of my wives.
好  乐队安排在这里
Okay, so this is where the band is.
吧台在这里
And this is where the bar is.
这些大头针上有人名
And all these pins have people's names on them.
瑞秋  你在这里
Rach, here you are.
为什么不给我一杯曼哈顿...
Why don't we just take me and put me with a Manattan in my hand...
让我和帅哥酒保聊天
...talking to the cute bartender.
这些大头针不是用来玩的  对吧
These pins aren't for playing, are they?
红的是我的客人  蓝色的是你的
The red ones are my guests, and the blue pins are yours.
真可怜  我只有10个客人
This is so sad. I only have like 10 pins.
钱德勒  放松  这又不是比赛
Chandler, relax. It's not a contest.
实力太悬殊了
Certainly not a close one.
好呀
Hello.
瑞秋
Hey, Rach.
不要再想了
Stop picturing it!
我觉得这样就可以了  座位表排好了
Okay. I think that's it. The seating chart is done.
这是我们的婚礼
This is our wedding.
他们看来玩得很开心  不是吗
They all look like they're having fun don't they?
我爸妈坐哪里
So where are my parents gonna be?
如果这是结婚礼堂...
Let's see. Well, if this is the wedding hall...
你父母会坐在皇后区的家里
...then your parents would be over here at home in Queens.
他们竟然没被邀请
They're not invited?
这太糟糕了  他们一定会很伤心
Oh, no, that's terrible. They're gonna be crushed!
为什么他们会以为自己被邀请了呢
Why would they think they're invited?
你问倒我了  我不...
You got me. I don't...
-乔伊  -我以为父母都会来嘛
- Joey! - I'm sorry. Look, I thought parents were coming.
你的父母会来  钱德勒的父母也会来
Your parents are coming. Chandler's parents are coming.
罗斯的父母也会来
Ross' parents are coming.
罗斯和我是一对爹妈生的
Ross' parents are my parents.
看  父母们都会来
Well, see, parents are coming.
我们应该邀请他们
You konw, I think we should invite them.
你只是想再添几枚蓝色大头针
Please, you just want more blue pins.
现在实在太惨了
Well, this is just sad.
好  也许能把他们排进来
All right. Maybe I can fit them in
不过要重新安排位子
if I just do some rearranging.
瑞秋可能要坐在吧台
Rachel may actually have to sit at the bar.
没有问题
That is not a problem.
也许你可以叫一杯桑格利塔酒
Maybe you'll order a little sangria.
去你的
Get out of here!
这是我们制作的礼服
These are our tuxedos that we make.
如果你有喜欢的  可以便宜些
If there's anything that you like, we can make a deal.
哪件都可以
Anything at all.
但这三件是莫妮卡事先核准的
But these are the three that Monica pre-approved.
谢谢你替我们拉到关系  瑞秋
Thanks a lot for hooking me up, Rach.
我想请你参加我们的婚礼  做我的客人
And I want you to know that I want you to attend our wedding as my guest.
我是莫妮卡的伴娘
I'm Monica's maid of honor.
别想把我变成蓝色大头针
Okay, don't try to blue-pin me.
这几件是什么情况  看着很不错
Well, what's the deal with these? these look nice.
是不错
They are nice.
这是为名人量身定做的
We custom-make tuxedos for celebrities
他们穿完之后会送回来
and then when they're done with them they just send them back.
-你是指像颁奖典礼之后  -有些是
- You mean like for award shows? - Some of them.
它们都上过红地毯
You mean these tuxes have been down the red carpet
听到人尖叫说
with people yelling,
"你穿的是什么牌子  你看着真时髦"
"Who are you wearing? You look fabulous!"
容我建议您多看看体育频道
Might I suggest watching a little more ESPN...
少看点艺人八封节目
...and a little less E!
谁穿过这些礼服
Okay. Who wore those?
-这是汤姆·布罗考穿过的  -不错嘛
- Well, this one's Tom Brokaw. - Not bad.
这是保罗·欧尼尔穿过的
This one is Paul O'Neill.
他是谁
Who's that?
他是洋基队的球员  说真的  多看体育台
He plays for the Yankees. Seriously, ESPN.
偶尔看一看  开着当背景也好
Just once in a while. Have it on in the background.
这是皮尔斯·布鲁斯南穿过的
This one was Pierce Brosnan.
皮尔斯·布鲁斯南
Pierce Brosnan?
真的吗
Are you serious?
这是詹姆斯·邦德的燕尾服
This is James Bond's tux?
我一定要穿詹姆斯·邦德的燕尾服结婚
I have to get married in James Bond's tux.
这件很酷
It's a pretty cool tux.
不仅如此
It's not just that.
我会是英格兰最强力的武器
I would be England's most powerful weapon.
女王陛下的秘密特务  四处奔波的断肠人
A jet-setting heartbreaker on Her Majesty's secret service.
持有杀人执照  天不怕地不怕的男人
A man who fears no one, with a license to kill.
莫妮卡会不会让我穿这件
Would Monica let me wear this?
我们应该学象棋的真正玩法
We should really learn how to play the real way.
我喜欢我们的玩法
I like our way.
将军
Chess!
-妙棋  -是啊
- Nice move. - Yeah.
乔伊  我替罗斯和钱德勒
So Joey I just hooked Ross and Chandler up
找到婚礼穿的燕尾服了  你需要吗
with some tuxedos for the wedding, do you need one?
不  我是主婚人  不穿燕尾服
No, I'm performing the ceremony. I'm not wearing a tux.
-那你要穿什么  -多彩长袍
- What are you gonna wear? - Multi-colored robes.
再戴顶帽子
And maybe a hat.
-莫妮卡知道吗  -不知道吧
- Does Monica know about this? - I don't think so.
你告诉她时  我可以在场吗
Can I please be there when you tell her?
晚上要不要去看电影
Rach, wait. You want to go to a movie tonight?
我去不成  我要和梅莉莎吃饭
You know what? I can't. I'm having dinner with that Melissa girl.
我可以去吗
Can I come?
我不出声  你只会听见我摄影机拍摄的声音
I won't even talk. You'll just hear the noise from my video camera.
什么情况  怎么回事
What is this? What's going on?
我可以告诉她吗
Can I tell her? Can I tell her?
你要听真实情况
Well, do you want to hear what actually happened
还是乔伊的淫荡版本
or Joey's lewd version?
-乔伊的版本  -好
- Joey's. - Okay.
我有个大学朋友
Come on. I had this friend from college ...
我不应该告诉乔伊  有一次...
...and I made the mistake of telling Joey that one time...
她和我接吻了...
...she and I, you know, kissed a little bit.
是啊  肯定有这么回事
Yeah, I'm sure that happened.
-是真的  -当然
- It did. - Sure.
真的发生了
Hey. It happened.
是大四那年  有次夏威夷舞会之后
It was senior year in college. It was after the Sigma Chi luau...
我和梅莉莎喝得大醉
...and Melissa and I got very drunk.
结果我们两个接吻了
And we ended up kissing.
好几分钟呢
For several minutes.
也就是说她喝了几杯汽酒
Which means she had a couple spritzers
轻轻吻在脸颊上
and a quick peck on the cheek.
你为什么要让我幻灭呢
Why are you taking this away from me?
你为什么就不相信呢
Why is it so hard for you to believe?
好吧  我不知道你是同性恋
Okay. I just didn't know that you were a lesbian.
我没说我是同性恋
I'm not saying that I'm a lesbian.
我只是说那件事真的发生了
I'm just saying that this happened.
这件事太狂野了  而你却这么地...
It just seems pretty wild. And you're so...
乖宝宝
...vanilla.
乖宝宝  我不是乖宝宝  我做很多疯狂的事
Vanilla? I'm not vanilla. I do lots of crazy things.
我喝醉了  在拉斯维加斯结了婚
I mean, I got drunk and married in Vegas.
和罗斯而已
To Ross.
如果你不相信我...
If you don't believe me about this,
今晚就和我一起去吃饭
why don't you just come with me to dinner tonight
她会告诉你的
and she'll tell you.
好吧  可是我想像不出来
Okay, all right. Because I can't picture it.
你该看看我脑袋里的画面
You should get inside my head.
猜我为你的婚礼搞到了什么
Guess what I got for your wedding?
头像晾衣架  瘦巴巴的女伴
A freakishly thin date with a hanger for a head?
瑞秋替我弄到一件燕尾服  但不是随便一件
Rachel hooked me up with a tux. But not just any tux.
是蝙蝠侠穿过的
Batman's tux!
-什么  -没错
- What? - That's right.
是为方·基默加急赶制的
Made expressly for Val Kilmer,
他穿着出演了票房冠军电影...
and worn by him in the hit film...
就是他演的那部蝙幅侠电影
...that Batman film he was in.
你不能穿那件  我才要穿名人的燕尾服
You can't wear that. I'm wearing the famous tux.
-詹姆斯·邦德的燕尾服  -怎样
- James Bond's tux! - So?
怎样  如果你穿那件  我就显不出特别了
So? If you wear that, it'll make mine less special.
你的大喜日子本身还不够特别吗
You need something to make this day special?
喂  你拥有最特别的一样
Hello! You have the most special thing of all.
你要迎娶你最爱的女人
You are marrying the woman you love.
不要抢走我的风头  拜托
Please don't take away my cool thing. Please. Pretty please?
"拜托"  这可不像007的语气
"Pretty please?" Not very 007.
那可是我的大喜日子
Look, it's my wedding day okay?
如果你要结婚  我不会做任何惹你生气的事
If you were getting married, I'd never do anything to upset you.
我结婚的时候  你和我妹妹上床了
When I got married you slept with my sister.
这点很像007
That was pretty 007.
真好  你来了  好  我想出办法了
Okay, good, you're here. All right, I figured it out.
我把这两桌的8个人  加上你父母...
I'm gonna take 2 tables of 8, add your parents...
变成3桌6个人
...and make them into 3 tables of 6.
我已经通知了宴会承包方  都搞定了
And I called the caterer. I added two extra meals, we are good to go!
他们不来了
Yeah. They're not coming.
什么
What?
他们觉得你是因为我才邀请他们的
Somehow, they got the idea that you only invited them because of me.
他们觉得自己不受欢迎
They feel a little unwanted.
太糟糕了  虽然话是没错  但太糟糕了
That's too bad. It's true. But too bad.
你可以打电话给我妈
Look, Mon. If you could just call my mom.
-乔伊  -来嘛
- Joey. - Come on.
告诉她你希望他们参加
Just let her know you really want them to be there.
别忘了  这些年来
Let's not forget, this is a woman
她可送过你不少千层面
who has sent you many lasagnas over the years.
没有啊
No, she hasn't.
有些没送到你手里又不是她的错
Is it her fault if some didn't make it to you?
我要说什么
What am I gonna say?
告诉她请贴搞乱了
Tell them you mixed up invitations.
不  怪邮局好了
No, no, no, blame it on the post office.
他们最恨邮局  还有爱尔兰人
They hate the post office. And the Irish.
不过你没理由怪到他们头上
But I don't think you could blame it on them, so...
喂  你好  崔比安尼太太
Hello? Yeah, hi. Mrs. Tribbiani?
我是莫妮卡·盖勒
This is Monica Geller.
我想告诉你  我和钱德勒
I'm just calling to say that Chandler and I
很希望你们能来参加婚礼
really hope you can make it to the wedding.
我们很多请贴都没寄到
Apparently a bunch of the invitations that we sent weren't delivered.
我猜又是可恶的邮局给搞丢了
I guess there was some screw-up at the damn post office.
就是嘛
Tell me about it!
什么美国邮局嘛  还不如叫美国遗失局
Yeah, the U.S. Post Office? No. More like U.S. Lost Office.
他们搞什么嘛  难道是爱尔兰人吗
What are they, Irish?
话说回来  他叫艾伦
Anyway, his name's Allen.
我们在一起三年了
And we've been going out for three years.
他是我做宴会策划的第一位客户
He was my first client when I became a party planner.
那时他正要给他女朋友策划宴会
He was actually planning a party for his girlfriend at the time.
-他是雪城大学贝塔兄弟会的  -真好
- And he was Theta Beta Pi at Syracuse. - That's great.
-你参加过姐妹会吗  -当然
- Phoebe, were you ever in a sorority? - Of course.
我是大腿卫生棉条的成员
Yes. I was a Thigh Mega Tampon.
哪一个
What one?
我们原本也很庞大  但后来被关掉了...
We were really huge too. But they had to shut us down...
因为瑞吉娜·费兰吉死于酒精中毒
...when Regina Phalangie died of alcohol poisoning.
真是糟糕  一个女孩就毁了整个姐妹会
Isn't it a shame when one girl ruins it for the whole bunch?
不管了...
Anyway...
说到喝太多
Speaking of drinking too much,
我告诉菲比在夏威夷舞会的疯狂之夜
I was telling Phoebe about that one crazy night
我们亲吻的事
after the Sigma Chi luau where we made out.
什么
What?
记得我们...
Remember we...
我们穿着纱笼裙  还有椰子壳的比基尼上衣
Come on, we had sarongs on and the coconut bikini tops.
之后我们回到家  脑筋变得不清楚
We went back to the house and got really silly...
然后我们接吻了
...and we made out.
瑞瑞  我不知道你在说什么
Wow, Ray-Ray, I have no idea what you're talking about.
真的吗
Really?
罗斯是蝙蝠侠
Ross is Batman.
他隐藏这个身份可真够久的
Well, he did manage to keep his identity secret for a long time.
瑞秋替罗斯弄到这件燕尾服
Rachel got Ross the tuxedo
方·基默在蝙蝠侠里穿的那件
that Val Kilmer wore in Batman.
蝙蝠侠比詹姆斯·邦德酷多了
Batman is so much cooler than James Bond.
什么  007有很多便携工具
What are you talking about? 007 has all those gadgets.
蝙蝠侠有万能腰带
Batman has a utility belt.
-007有高级跑车  -蝙蝠侠有蝙蝠车
- 007 has a fancy car. - Batman has the Batmobile.
007坐拥佳丽
007 gets all the ladies.
蝙蝠侠有罗宾
Batman has Robin.
咱家有体育台吧
We get ESPN, right?
你何不穿上你的007燕尾服
How about you go put on your 007 tuxedo,
我替你调一杯马丁尼
and I'll make you a nice martini?
我不喜欢马丁尼
Actually, I don't like martinis.
-一杯摇摇饮料加一根搞笑吸管  -帅气
- How about a Yoo-hoo with a funny straw? - Yum.
请贴上写的是晚上六点
I know the invitation says 6 o'clock.
是指六点入席
But does that mean you want people to get there at 6,
还是六点开始表演
or the show's gonna start right at 6?
"表演"
"The show"?
对  婚礼  骗到你了
Right, right, the wedding. Gotcha.
不过婚礼会晚一点开始  是吧
But I mean, it's gonna start a little late right?
婚礼都会拖延一会再开始
I mean, weddings start late. Right?
你那是没参加过我的婚礼吧
Have you ever been to one of my weddings?
问题是那天我侄女受洗...
Well, the thing is it's the same day as my niece's christening...
我希望我父母能及时赶到见到我
and I really want my parents to be there in time to see me.
因为我的主婚仪式在开始阶段
Because my part's in the beginning.
我不参加其他部份的表演...婚礼
I'm not in the rest of the show... Wedding.
婚礼六点开始
The wedding starts at 6.
好  我明白了
Okay. I totally hear you.
这样如何  我可以即兴表演到他们到场
How about this? I vamp a little till they get there.
你要"即兴表演"
You'll "vamp"?
就像是暖场之类的  问他们从哪里来
Yeah, like warm up the crowd. Ask where they're from.
因为有乔伊·崔比安尼在场
Because in Joey Tribbiani,
你便同时拥有了牧师和演员
you get a minister and you got an entertainer.
我是一位"牧演员"
I'm a "ministainer." All right?
没人比我更强  我就是王中之王
There's no one better. There's no one greater.
你怎么能不记得我们接吻的事
How can you not remember us kissing?
我不知道  没发生过的事我怎么能记得
I don't know. I don't remember a lot of things that never happened.
记得我们在凉台上
Come on, remember, we were on the sleeping porch?
不停地傻笑
We couldn't stop giggling.
我们的椰子壳撞在一起
Our coconuts kept knocking together.
乔伊的脑袋在某处爆炸了
Somewhere Joey's head is exploding.
抱歉  我不想把你搞得不自在
Listen, I'm sorry. I don't want to make you uncomfortable...
但我告诉菲比发生过这种事  她不相信我
but I told Phoebe that it happened, and she doesn't believe me.
对不起  瑞瑞
I'm sorry, Ray-Ray.
如果真的发生过这种事  我会承认的
I mean, if I thought it happened, I would say it.
也许我昏过去了  你在我睡觉时对我做了什么
Maybe I passed out and you did stuff to me while I was sleeping.
没有
No!
没关系  你不必逼她说  我相信你
Rachel, it's okay, you don't have to do this. I believe you.
如果你说你吻了梅莉莎
Okay, if you say that you kissed Melissa,
那么你就吻了梅莉莎
then you kissed Melissa.
-谢谢  菲比  -好
- Thank you, Phoebe. - Okay.
-可是她没有  -我知道
- But she didn't. - I know.
你就带着它走来走去
Do you just carry that around?
是的  我发现这是个好话题
Yes. I find it to be something of a conversation piece.
-和谁之间  -甘瑟
- Between you and...? - Gunther.
我们何不穿上
Why don't we put them on?
拍张蝙蝠侠和詹姆斯·邦德的合影
Get a picture of Batman and James Bond, together.
我很愿意  但我的裤子有点紧
I would, but mine doesn't fit. The pants are a little tight.
只是有点紧吗
A little tight?
我都能看到里面的两个0和一个7了
I could see 00 and 7 in those things.
真糟糕
Well, that stinks.
我很期待和你一起穿名人燕尾服呢
I was looking forward to wearing our celebrity tuxes together.
所以你也不穿了吗
So you're not gonna be wearing yours?
你开什么玩笑  这可是蝙蝠侠的燕尾服
Are you kidding? It's Batmars tux!
我试穿看看
Let me try it on.
好  只穿外套就好
Okay. But just the jacket.
两个0和一个7不要搀和进去
00 and 7 are not getting in there.
好
Okay.
双面通风超舒适  蝙蝠侠
Holy double-vented comfort, Batman!
这是什么
What's this?
《真情难舍》首映请贴
An invitation to the At First Sight premiere?
方·基默没在《蝙蝠侠》里穿这件燕尾服
Oh, my god. Val Kilmer didn't wear this in Batman.
他穿这件去参加了那部文艺爱情片的首映
He wore it to the premiere of some tooty-fruity love story
他不过演了个瞎子
where he played a blind guy.
给我看
Let me see that.
老天啊
Oh, man.
你唯一的超能力
The only super power you have
不过是稍显敏感的嗅觉
is the slightly heightened sense of smell.
可以和你们谈谈吗
Monica, Chandler, can I talk to you guys for a second?
我放弃了  你要怎样就怎样吧
That's it. I give up. Whatever you want, you can have it.
你要唱歌还是跳舞
You want to sing a song, you want to do a dance?
还是要你妈在祭坛前大叫种族歧视的字眼
You want your mom to stand at the altar screaming racial slurs?
我都不在乎
I don't care.
我只是想来谢谢你们
No, I just want to thank you guys
为我父母做的一切
for what you did for my parents. That was really sweet.
他们很高兴能出席你们的大喜日子
They're so happy to be a part of your special day.
告诉他们我们很高兴他们能来
You're welcome. Tell them we're glad they're coming.
我会的
Okay, I will.
看看他们替我准备参加婚礼的衣服
Oh, check out what they got me to wear for the ceremony!
我替你们主婚时这样戴  然后...
I wear it like this when I marry you guys. And then this...
在宴会时这样戴
...is for party time.
那件事发生过  我告诉绝对发生过
It happened. I am telling you it happened.
很高兴认识你
It was great meeting you.
瑞秋  我大概不会打电话给你了  因为
And, Rachel? I don't think I'll be calling you because...
你变得好奇怪
...you know, you've gotten weird.
保重  两位
Take care, you guys.
等一下  好吧
Wait a minute. No, wait a minute. Okay, look.
那晚是我这辈子做过最狂野的一件事
That night was the one wild thing I've ever done in my entire life.
不能让你随便就给抹杀了
I'm not gonna let you take it away from me.
你要是不记得那件事  你大概会记得这个
So if you don't remember that, maybe you'll remember this...
天啊  你爱我
Oh, my God. You love me.
什么
What?
我当然记得  这些日子里我一直惦记着
Of course I remember our kiss. I think about it all the time.
椰子壳的撞击声还在我耳畔萦绕
I can still hear the coconuts knocking together...
我不想告诉你
I just didn't want to tell you,
因为我觉得你不会回应我的爱
because I didn't think you'd return my love and now that you have...
看是谁突然变得害羞了
Look who's being suddenly shy.
你一定和我有相同的感觉
You can't tell me you don't feel what I feel.
如果不是真心  是不会吻得那么好
Nobody can kiss that good and not mean it.
我就是吻功很好而已
I'm just a good kisser.
闭嘴
Shut up.
对不起
I'm sorry.
你不必抱歉
You don't have to be sorry.
我显然是在开玩笑
I'm obviously kidding.
我没爱上你  我没爱上她
I'm not in love with you. I'm not in love with her.
我没听到椰子壳撞击的声音
I don't hear coconuts banging together.
我和男友做爱时没有幻想你的模样
I don't picture your face when I make love to my boyfriend.
我要走了
Anyway, I gotta go.
吻别吧
A kiss goodbye?
不要  好吧
No? Okay.
我不知道会发生...
I mean, I had no idea that that would...
你这是什么意思
What the hell was that?
想看看那姑娘为什么那么纠结
Just wanted to see what all the fuss was about.
-然后呢  -我经历过更棒的
- And? - I've had better.
我找到一件合身的
All right. I found one that fits.
是啊  人们常说第23次时常出现奇迹
Well, you know what they say? 23rd time's a charm.
看看你  好英俊
Look at you, all handsome.
-这是谁穿过的  -有什么关系吗
- Whose is it? - Does it matter?
最重要的是你看来很英俊
All that matters is that you look so handsome.
-是谁  -我不想说
- Whose is it? - I don't want to say.
我不在乎  说嘛  是谁的
Come on, I don't care. Come on, whose is it?
黛安·基顿[女演员]
Diane Keaton.